This next exercise goes along with one of the previous exercises the ab-ductors.
This is for the abductors, your inner tight muscles.
It's important to work with this exercise because it will help give you balance and support especially in other exercises down the road.
Also your abductors coincide in a support mechanism with the obliques.
So if you're looking for some nice abs, doing these inner tight muscles will help it along.
Go ahead sit on the machine and make sure your pelvis is against the back of the seat.
Then lift the lever and slide the stirrups out as wide as you can with a comfortableness in your legs.
Don't go too wide but go wide enough so you can feel that your inner tight muscles are stretching as far as the can without any discomfort.
Then as you close your knees together and your feet together be sure to exhale and tighten up your abdominals.
All the while try to remain nice and tall through your spine as you work and keep refirming contractions through your abdominals as you close your legs.
Go for it!